http://www.worldofchristmas.net/privacy-policy.html

Privacy Policy
We honor your right to privacy and will remove your data from our systems if you wish us to do so.
Cookies
Learn more about Manage Cookies
A small text file may be placed on your computer by this Website when you visit certain parts of the Website and/or when you use certain features of the Website.
On worldofchristmas.net, privacy issues are a high priority for us and we follow standard industry practices to maintain your personal information. We respect your privacy and are committed to the same.
Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy.
1. Privacy Policy Coverage
worldofchristmas Privacy Policy covers treatment of personally identifiable information that we collect when you are on the worldofchristmas.net site.
2. Information collected by worldofchristmas.net
worldofchristmas.net collects personally identifiable information when during registration, worldofchristmas.net asks for your name and email address. Once you have sent us this information and sign in to our services you are not anonymous to us anymore.
We will retain any Data you submit for as long as worldofchristmas.net deems it necessary to provide adequate service to the User, unless explicitly asked by a User for their Data to be deleted.
3. Use of information by worldofchristmas.net
worldofchristmas.net uses information collected for two purposes:
(a) Information provided to us is used to customize the advertising and content you see and to inform you about special offers, new products and other services which are offered completely free of cost. worldofchristmas.net will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to third parties. Unless it is specifically stated otherwise. If data is being collected and/or maintained by any company other than worldofchristmas.net, you will be notified prior to the data collection or transfer.
(b) worldofchristmas.net may disclose personally identifiable information about you to third parties when:
we have your consent to share the information
we need to share your information to provide the product or service you have requested and given your consent
we have to cooperate with the investigations for unlawful activities
4. Collection of Information by Third Parties
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, you can visit www.networkadvertising.org.
Our members are our assets and we will never knowingly do anything to harm this trust. Any information given voluntarily to us by you is used to enhance your experience on our site, to provide you with interactive or personalized elements on the sites and to better prepare for future content based on your areas of interests. We gather this information to determine which areas are liked by our site members and which are not liked based on the traffic to those areas.
We don't track what individual members read, but rather try to determine how well each page performs. This helps us continue to provide better services to you. We also use the information that is gathered to tailor the content to best suit your needs and help our advertisers better understand our members.
Third-Party Privacy Policies
Third-party vendors use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to our website and/or other websites.
Here is a list of each third-party advertising vendor we work with along with a link to their privacy policy.
Google AdSense And It's Partners
1. Index Exchange
2. Google DFP/AdX
3. OpenX
4. App Nexus
5. Rubicon Project
6. Conversant
7. Sovrn
28. Adobe Advertising Cloud
29. AdRoll, Inc.
30. AdTriba
31. advanced STORE GmbH
32. Adventori
33. advolution.control
34. affilinet
35. Akamai
36. Amazon
37. Amobee
38. Analights
39. AppLovin Corp.
40. AppNexus
41. Arrivalist
42. AudienceProject
43. Aunica
44. Avocet
45. Bannerflow
46. Batch Media
47. BDSK Handels GmbH & Co. KG
120. Manage.com
121. Marketing Science Consulting Group, Inc.
122. MBR Targeting Gmbh
123. MediaMath
124. Meetrics
125. MindTake Research
126. Mobitrans
127. Mobpro
128. Moloco Ads
129. MSI-ACI
200. UDG
201. usemax (Emego GmbH)
202. Videology
203. Vimeo
204. Virtual Minds
205. Vodafone GmbH
206. Waystack
207. Weborama
208. White Ops
209. Widespace
210. Wizaly
211. Yieldr
212. ZMS
Google Analytics Privacy Notice
Our website uses Google Analytics to collect information about the use of our website. Google Analytics collects information from users such as how often they visit our website, what pages they visit, and what other websites they have used before coming to our website. We use the information we get from Google Analytics to analyze traffic and to improve our website. Google Analytics collects only the IP address assigned to you on the date you visit our website, not your name or other identifying information. We do not combine the information collected using Google Analytics with any personally identifiable information. Although Google Analytics plants a permanent cookie on your web browser to identify you as a unique user the next time you visit our website, the cookie cannot be used by anyone but Google. Google also uses specific identifiers to help collect information about the use of our website. For more information on how Google collects and processes your data, visit Google's Privacy and Terms. You can prevent Google Analytics from using your information by opting-out.
5. Links to other websites
This Website may, from time to time, provide links to other websites. We have no control over such websites and are not responsible for the content of these websites.
This privacy policy does not extend to your use of such websites. You are advised to read the privacy policy or statement of other websites prior to using them.
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.
Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.
Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.
